<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<sector boes="2.0.0">
    <name>Part 2: Exploration</name>
    <comment>Comment</comment>
    <sign id="0">
        <![CDATA[West - Marshy Tower|East - Lake Tower|South - Vault Tower]]>
    </sign>
    <area top="25" left="6" bottom="36" right="21">Path to Marshy Tower</area>
    <area top="37" left="7" bottom="41" right="22">Backwoods</area>
    <area top="31" left="23" bottom="43" right="25">Road to Vault Tower</area>
    <area top="27" left="26" bottom="30" right="29">Road to Lake Tower</area>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[You're now exploring the great outdoors! When outdoors, each tile on the map represents a larger space, so each move you make takes more in-game time.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[In the outdoors, you'll find entrances to towns or dungeons like the tower from which you're emerging now.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[Clearing many BoE scenarios usually requires a thorough exploration of the outdoors and every town or dungeon you can find. First of all, you should open your minimap to help keep track of where you've been! Type 'a' to do so.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="6">
        <![CDATA[To read a sign, use the Look command. You can do this by typing 'l' or clicking the button of the eye. You have to be standing next to things  like signs or books to investigate them closely.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA[You can also look by right-clicking.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[The terrain is getting wilder as you make your way westward. You should move diagonally to avoid dangerous terrain where possible, but this might not always be possible.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[It seems like this road leads to one of the towers you need to visit, but the woods have overgrown the path. There must be another way around.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[You can see a tower across the water, but there's no ferry or bridge to take you across. Frustrating.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[You have found your way back onto the overgrown road to Vault Tower!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[In the outdoors, if you're not poisoned and you have enough food, you can rest to recover your health and spell points.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="18">
        <![CDATA[Type 'r', or click the button of a tent, to do this.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="19">
        <![CDATA[If you're ever low on food, Michael has a priest spell (Manna) which will summon some!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22" />
</sector>
