<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<town boes="2.0.0">
    <size>48</size>
    <name>Vault Tower</name>
    <comment>Comment 1</comment>
    <comment>Comment 2</comment>
    <comment>Comment 3</comment>
    <bounds top="3" left="3" bottom="44" right="44" />
    <difficulty>0</difficulty>
    <lighting>lit</lighting>
    <timer freq="10">18</timer>
    <timer freq="2">32</timer>
    <flags>
        <chop kills="30000" />
    </flags>
    <item id="0">
        <type>0</type>
        <charges>500</charges>
        <property>true</property>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <creature id="0">
        <type>19</type>
        <attitude>friendly</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>20</personality>
        <face>10</face>
    </creature>
    <creature id="1">
        <type>19</type>
        <attitude>friendly</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>21</personality>
        <face>71</face>
        <ontalk>23</ontalk>
    </creature>
    <creature id="2">
        <type>19</type>
        <attitude>friendly</attitude>
        <mobility>0</mobility>
        <personality>22</personality>
        <face>10</face>
        <onkill>36</onkill>
    </creature>
    <sign id="0">
        <![CDATA[Vault Tower -|NO BREAKING AND ENTERING]]>
    </sign>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[This appears to be the central chamber of the vault! And right here, is the artifact piece you're looking for.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[You've reached Vault Tower. This building is in better repair than the last one, and the front door is locked. Thissa says, "I can break thissss!"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[It may be rude, but the life of an adventurer involves breaking the rules (and other people's property) sometimes. When you try to open a locked door, you'll have the option to bash it down. When asked, choose your physically strongest character, and give it your best shot.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="7">
        <![CDATA["Whoa there!"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[Oops. Of course this place is guarded.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="9">
        <![CDATA["The boss will make me pay for that door, you know! Fix it or I'll have to follow the 'violent repulsion' protocol."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[You can close doors behind you with the Use command, which might come in handy for sneaking around. Type 'u' or click the 'Use' button, and see if you can get this door back on its hinges.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA["Oi! I said, fix the door."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA["I'll tell you what. I wouldn't mind a piece of the boss's treasure. Listen to me, and I'll tell you how to get in. We can split the stash."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[Press 't', or the button with a mouth on it, then select a creature to start a conversation.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="20">
        <![CDATA["Hey hotshot! You'll want to give those lockpicks to your wiliest thief and equip them by clicking on them in the items panel."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="21">
        <![CDATA[To view a different character's inventory, click their name in the stats panel at the top-right. If Frrrrrr isn't holding the lockpicks, select whoever is. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[To give an item from one character to another click the button with a 'G' next to the lockpicks. Select Frrrrrr, who is your best lockpicker right now. Then make sure they're equipped.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="26">
        <![CDATA[The guard changes positions.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="27">
        <![CDATA[The guard watching through this window stops you. "Hey! Move any further and I'll shoot."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[Maybe your buddy in the first room can help with this. (People might respond differently to the same questions after something specific happens.)]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[You can ask people about things that aren't shown as buttons in the dialog window. Click 'Ask About' or type 'a' to do so, then type what you want to ask about.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[This guard will respond to the words 'patrol' or 'duty'!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="31">
        <![CDATA[No sense in turning around now!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="32">
        <![CDATA[Adrianna examines this door closely. "The lock is sealed magically," she observes. "I have a spell for that."]]>
    </string>
    <string id="33">
        <![CDATA[Cast the mage spell 'Unlock Doors' as a third option for tricky doors where bashing or picking doesn't cut it!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="34">
        <![CDATA[You take it, and the gate opens.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="35">
        <![CDATA[The sneaky guard turns and flees from your presence, passing right through the wall to the east!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="36">
        <![CDATA[(If you're ever stuck in a scenario, try moving into suspicious walls. Even if they're not  breakable with magic, you might find a hidden door!) ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[Excellent! A boat. This should take you along the water to the final Tower!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="38">
        <![CDATA[Move onto the boat to board it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="43">
        <![CDATA[Having struck down your duplicitous collaborator, you notice something strange about the wall to the east.]]>
    </string>
</town>
