<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<town boes="2.0.0">
    <size>48</size>
    <name>Marshy Tower</name>
    <comment>Comment 1</comment>
    <comment>Comment 2</comment>
    <comment>Comment 3</comment>
    <bounds top="3" left="3" bottom="34" right="47" />
    <difficulty>0</difficulty>
    <lighting>lit</lighting>
    <timer freq="2">13</timer>
    <timer freq="0">0</timer>
    <flags>
        <chop kills="30000" />
    </flags>
    <item id="0">
        <type>109</type>
    </item>
    <item id="1">
        <type>103</type>
    </item>
    <item id="2">
        <type>106</type>
    </item>
    <item id="3">
        <type>106</type>
    </item>
    <item id="4">
        <type>155</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="5">
        <type>19</type>
    </item>
    <item id="6">
        <type>19</type>
    </item>
    <item id="7">
        <type>0</type>
        <charges>50</charges>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <creature id="0">
        <type>118</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>0</face>
        <onkill>9</onkill>
    </creature>
    <creature id="1">
        <type>118</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>0</face>
        <onkill>9</onkill>
    </creature>
    <creature id="2">
        <type>118</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>0</face>
        <onkill>9</onkill>
    </creature>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[Your priest, Michael, stops the party. "Let's not go in anywhere dangerous while any of us are poisoned. I'll cure us by pressing 'p' or the ankh button to open the Priest Spells menu, choosing myself as the caster, choosing Cure Poison, then choosing a target, and pressing 'cast.'"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[This tower is slowly sinking into the marsh. Not fast enough to be of concern for you, though.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[Your expedition has hit another snag. This abandoned security checkpoint  shows no way of opening from the outside.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[Michael points to a crack in the wall. "I can break that with another Priest spell!"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="9">
        <![CDATA[You can also cast Priest spells using the 'Cast Priest' menu at the top of the screen. First, click Michael's name in the 'Party Stats' panel in the upper right, to select him.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[Then, cast the Priest spell 'Move Mountains' and select the cracked wall to destroy it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[Whenever this tower was last occupied, some supplies were left here for guards on duty. You can search containers by looking at them with 'l'/right-click, and you can take items you find lying around by pressing 'g' or the hand button.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[With no way around the rubble in the main hall, you wander into the dining hall. Maybe it connects with another part of the tower.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[Oh, no! This pantry has been infested with giant spiders.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[Press 'f' to enter combat mode. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[Now that the spiders are dead, you probably want to clean off their webs. Control+w, or Command+w on a Mac, will make the party rest for a short time in town or a dungeon, long enough to clean off any webs. You can also select 'Wait 80 Moves' in the Action menu.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[You can also clean webs off of map tiles by clicking the 'Use' button (or typing 'u') and selecting a tile with webs on it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[Press 'f' again, or click the Sword button, to end combat mode.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[timer called]]>
    </string>
    <string id="31">
        <![CDATA[Once again, Michael recognizes a weakened spot in the wall where mold has grown through the bricks. Casting Move Mountains here will make the opening you need to explore further.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="32">
        <![CDATA[(When building your own party, you should probably always give at least one of your characters 2 levels of Priest Spells skill! Some older scenarios assume you will be able to cast Move Mountains, and to recognize vulnerable walls. You can get stuck without it.)]]>
    </string>
    <string id="37">
        <![CDATA[Through the gate, you see what remains of a courtyard. The first artifact piece is in there! Too bad the gate won't open.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="38">
        <![CDATA[You collect the first piece of the artifact! It's wet....]]>
    </string>
    <string id="39">
        <![CDATA[Finally! A mechanism for opening one of these gates.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="40">
        <![CDATA[You can operate most levers by using, looking, or moving onto them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="45">
        <![CDATA[More concerning, is how the portcullis clangs shut behind you!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="46">
        <![CDATA[Well, with the front gate now closed, you'll need to find another way out.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="47">
        <![CDATA[You see a window high in the southern wall of this chapel. Maybe you could crawl through it, if only you could stand on something tall.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="48">
        <![CDATA[Like that altar! The gods won't mind if you move their idols aside... probably.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="49">
        <![CDATA[Click the 'Use' button, or type 'u', then select a tile to use it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="53">
        <![CDATA[Disease is an extremely unpleasant status to have. Michael has a priest spell, Cure Disease, that can fix it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="54">
        <![CDATA[There appears to be a small chapel here. Maybe you can look into it after searching the courtyard to the north.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="55">
        <![CDATA[This book describes how to cast a new priest spell: Disease.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="56">
        <![CDATA[This book describes how to cast a new priest spell: Cure Disease.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="57">
        <![CDATA[Adrianna and Feodoric can cast mage spells. Press 'm' on their turn, use the 'Cast Mage' menu item, or click the flaming orb button to do so. Lots of mage spells are useful in combat! Try Flame or Fireball for wiping out enemies early on.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="63">
        <![CDATA[Frrrrrr comes prepared with a bow and arrow. To fire, type 's' or click the button of an arrow, then select a tile with an enemy on it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="64">
        <![CDATA[You'll want to keep stocked up on arrows, but Frrrrrr can also wield melee weapons if you find an extra for them.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="69">
        <![CDATA[Priests are useful in combat, too! They have spells like Wound for dealing damage, Stumble for disabling enemies, or Charm Foe for turning enemies against each other.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="70">
        <![CDATA[Most importantly, though, they can heal your party when someone's injured!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="71">
        <![CDATA[(Feodoric can also cast some priest spells.)]]>
    </string>
    <string id="75">
        <![CDATA[Start combat mode before going in there!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="76">
        <![CDATA[There are MANY other spells in Blades of Exile! To learn how any other spell works,  open the Mage or Priest spells menu, then hold the Alt key (or Option key on a Mac) while clicking on the spell.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="82">
        <![CDATA[Through this portcullis, you can see the next piece of the artifact. But you can't get it open.]]>
    </string>
</town>
