<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<town boes="2.0.0">
    <size>24</size>
    <name>Part 1: Lore</name>
    <comment>Comment 1</comment>
    <comment>Comment 2</comment>
    <comment>Comment 3</comment>
    <bounds top="3" left="3" bottom="20" right="20" />
    <difficulty>0</difficulty>
    <lighting>lit</lighting>
    <flags>
        <chop kills="30000" />
    </flags>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[This room contains multiple books explaining the almost 30-year history of Blades of Exile! To read one, you must be standing next to it. Then, either right-click its space, or click the eye button in your hotbar (hotkey: 'l' for look) before selecting its space.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[Try glancing at at least one of them before you rush off through the portal to the north.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[happened]]>
    </string>
    <string id="3">
        <![CDATA["What in the world is a Role-Playing Game?"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="4">
        <![CDATA[A primer for the TRULY uninitiated.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="9">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[Do you remember being young and pretending you were a knight or a wizard or a space explorer? Or maybe you pretended to be one of those things just yesterday. Whenever it last happened, you were role-playing.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="11">
        <![CDATA[Role-Playing Games are structured ways to imagine being someone, somewhere, or someTHING else. People play RPGs to experience relief from normal, restrictive life, or to process intense subjects that might feel inappropriate in a casual conversation. Sometimes both at the same time!]]>
    </string>
    <string id="12">
        <![CDATA[Fantasy RPGs like this one set up a rich and often magical environment where you get to be the hero. With enough training and tactical know-how, you can stand up to any threat you come across.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="13">
        <![CDATA[In Blades of Exile you will control a party of adventurers fighting monsters, exploring treacherous dungeons, and navigating political intrigue. All of that can get pretty complicated, especially because this game was created in 1997, a time when you could be expected to read an entire manual BEFORE launching anything on your computer.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[We (the small group of volunteers working to preserve this game) want as many people as possible to enjoy it, and that includes you! Even if you've never played an RPG before. This tutorial is our best effort at helping you get started.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
    <string id="18">
        <![CDATA[*]]>
    </string>
</town>
