<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<town boes="2.0.0">
    <size>48</size>
    <name>Marshy Tower</name>
    <comment>Comment 1</comment>
    <comment>Comment 2</comment>
    <comment>Comment 3</comment>
    <bounds top="3" left="3" bottom="44" right="44" />
    <difficulty>0</difficulty>
    <lighting>lit</lighting>
    <timer freq="2">13</timer>
    <timer freq="2">17</timer>
    <flags>
        <chop kills="30000" />
    </flags>
    <item id="0">
        <type>109</type>
    </item>
    <item id="1">
        <type>103</type>
    </item>
    <item id="2">
        <type>106</type>
    </item>
    <item id="3">
        <type>106</type>
    </item>
    <item id="4">
        <type>155</type>
        <contained>true</contained>
    </item>
    <item id="5">
        <type>19</type>
    </item>
    <item id="6">
        <type>19</type>
    </item>
    <creature id="0">
        <type>118</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>0</face>
        <onkill>9</onkill>
    </creature>
    <creature id="1">
        <type>118</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>0</face>
        <onkill>9</onkill>
    </creature>
    <creature id="2">
        <type>118</type>
        <attitude>hostile-a</attitude>
        <mobility>1</mobility>
        <personality>-1</personality>
        <face>0</face>
        <onkill>9</onkill>
    </creature>
    <string id="0">
        <![CDATA[Your priest, Michael, stops the party. "Let's not go in anywhere dangerous while any of us are poisoned. I'll cure us by pressing 'p' to open the Priest Spells menu, choosing myself as the caster, choosing Cure Poison, then choosing a target, and pressing 'cast.'"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="1">
        <![CDATA[This tower is slowly sinking into the marsh. Not fast enough to be of concern for you, though.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="2">
        <![CDATA[Your expedition has hit another snag. This abandoned security checkpoint  shows no way of opening from the outside.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="8">
        <![CDATA[Michael points to a crack in the wall. "I can break that with another Priest spell!"]]>
    </string>
    <string id="9">
        <![CDATA[You can also cast Priest spells using the 'Cast Priest' menu at the top of the screen. First, click Michael's name in the 'Party Stats' panel in the upper right, to select him.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="10">
        <![CDATA[Then, cast the Priest spell 'Move Mountains' and select the cracked wall to destroy it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="14">
        <![CDATA[Whenever this tower was last occupied, some supplies were left here for guards on duty. You can search containers by looking at them with 'l'/right-click, and you can take items you find lying around by pressing 'g' or the hand button.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="15">
        <![CDATA[With no way around the rubble in the main hall, you wander into the dining hall. Maybe it connects with another part of the tower.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="16">
        <![CDATA[Oh, no! This pantry has been infested with giant spiders.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="17">
        <![CDATA[Press 'f' to enter combat mode. ]]>
    </string>
    <string id="18">
        <![CDATA[Adrianna and Feodoric can cast mage spells. Press 'm' on their turn, use the 'Cast Mage' menu item, or click the flaming orb mutton to do so. Lots of mage spells are useful in combat! Try Flame or Fireball for wiping out enemies early on.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="22">
        <![CDATA[Now that the spiders are dead, you probably want to clean off their webs. Control+w, or Command+w on a Mac, will make the party rest for a short time in town or a dungeon, long enough to clean off any webs. You can also select 'Wait 80 Moves' in the Action menu.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="28">
        <![CDATA[You can also clean webs off of map tiles by clicking the 'Use' button (or typing 'u') and selecting a tile with webs on it.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="29">
        <![CDATA[Press 'f' again, or click the Sword button, to end combat mode.]]>
    </string>
    <string id="30">
        <![CDATA[timer called]]>
    </string>
</town>
